ilovefunnypics.com 2013-05-15

# Privacy Policy | ilovefunnypics.com

Your Privacy  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, iBroke has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Collection of Personal Information  
When visiting ilovefunnypics, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Changes to this Privacy Statement  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of ilovefunnypics then you may contact us at ilovefunnypics.contact@gmail.com

DCMA

Copyright Infringement  
A. If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any User Submission or other content infringes upon your copyrights, you may submit a notification pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) by providing our Copyright Agent with the following information in writing (see 17 U.S.C 512(c)(3) for further detail):  
1\. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;  
2\. Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;  
3\. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material;  
4\. Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail;  
5\. A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and  
6\. A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.  
ilovefunnypics’s designated Copyright Agent to receive notifications of claimed infringement is:  
Attention: Copyright Agent  
ilovefunnypics  
1421 n orchard beach dr  
port clinton,oh 43452

You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the requirements of this Section 8(A) your DMCA notice may not be
